export const chapter = "Chapter - 7: circulatory and Excretory systems  ";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "What is the main function of the circulatory system in the body?",
          optionA: "Absorb nutrients from food",
          optionB: "Transport substances inside the body",
          optionC: "Remove waste from the body",
          correctAnswer: "Transport substances inside the body",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the size of the heart, approximately?",
          optionA: "The size of a basketball",
          optionB: "The size of a fist",
          optionC: "The size of a tennis ball",
          correctAnswer: "The size of a fist",
        },
        {
          question: "What gives the red color to blood?",
          optionA: "Oxygen",
          optionB: "Hemoglobin",
          optionC: "Carbon dioxide",
          correctAnswer: "Hemoglobin",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which blood vessels carry blood from the heart to different parts of the body?",
          optionA: "Veins",
          optionB: "Arteries",
          optionC: "Capillaries",
          correctAnswer: "Arteries",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the purpose of the excretory system in the body?",
          optionA: "Absorb nutrients",
          optionB: "Transport oxygen",
          optionC: "Remove waste",
          correctAnswer: "Remove waste",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the function of the kidneys in the excretory system?",
          optionA: "Pump blood",
          optionB: "Produce urine",
          optionC: "Filter the blood",
          correctAnswer: "Filter the blood",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the role of urethra in the excretory system?",
          optionA: "Filter urine",
          optionB: "Store urine",
          optionC: "Remove urine from the body",
          correctAnswer: "Remove urine from the body",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which organs, in addition to the kidneys, are part of the excretory system?",
          optionA: "Lungs and liver",
          optionB: "Ureters and urinary bladder",
          optionC: "Heart and skin",
          correctAnswer: "Ureters and urinary bladder",
        },
        {
          question: "How is carbon dioxide primarily removed from the body?",
          optionA: "Through the skin",
          optionB: "Through the kidneys",
          optionC: "Through the lungs",
          correctAnswer: "Through the lungs",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Why does the urinary bladder stretch, giving the urge to urinate?",
          optionA: "To absorb nutrients",
          optionB: "To store excess water",
          optionC: "To store urine",
          correctAnswer: "To store urine",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "The pumping movement of the heart while it pumps blood is called __________.",
          optionA: "Pulse",
          optionB: "Circulation",
          optionC: "Heartbeat",
          correctAnswer: "Heartbeat",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Blood vessels that carry blood from the heart to different parts of the body are called __________.",
          optionA: "Veins",
          optionB: "Capillaries",
          optionC: "Arteries",
          correctAnswer: "Arteries",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Blood is a fluid that flows throughout our body and carries __________ in it.",
          optionA: "Nutrients, oxygen, and water",
          optionB: "Carbon dioxide and other waste",
          optionC: "Blood cells",
          correctAnswer: "Nutrients, oxygen, and water",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The excretory system consists of a pair of kidneys, a pair of ureters, a urinary bladder, and a __________.",
          optionA: "Urethra",
          optionB: "Heart",
          optionC: "Lungs",
          correctAnswer: "Urethra",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Kidneys filter the blood, and the harmful and toxic products are removed from blood as it passes through the kidneys, forming __________.",
          optionA: "Saliva",
          optionB: "Urine",
          optionC: "Blood cells",
          correctAnswer: "Urine",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The tubes that carry urine from the kidneys to the urinary bladder are called __________.",
          optionA: "Arteries",
          optionB: "Ureters",
          optionC: "Veins",
          correctAnswer: "Ureters",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The urinary bladder stores urine, and its walls get stretched when urine is stored, causing the urge to __________.",
          optionA: "Eat",
          optionB: "Drink",
          optionC: "Urinate",
          correctAnswer: "Urinate",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Carbon dioxide is removed from the body when we breathe out with the help of our __________.",
          optionA: "Kidneys",
          optionB: "Liver",
          optionC: "Lungs",
          correctAnswer: "Lungs",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Our skin produces sweat primarily to keep our body cool and helps to remove excess salts and other wastes, acting as an additional __________.",
          optionA: "Heart",
          optionB: "Liver",
          optionC: "Excretory organ",
          correctAnswer: "Excretory organ",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The circulatory system consists of the heart, blood, and __________.",
          optionA: "Kidneys",
          optionB: "Skin",
          optionC: "Blood vessels",
          correctAnswer: "Blood vessels",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question: "The heart is located outside the chest cavity.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Veins carry blood from different parts of the body to the heart.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Blood vessels include arteries, veins, and capillaries.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The excretory system includes the kidneys, ureters, urinary bladder, and urethra.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "The formation of urine takes place in the lungs.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Urethra is the opening through which urine is removed from the body.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "The skin produces sweat primarily to keep the body warm.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Carbon dioxide is removed from the body when we breathe out with the help of our kidneys.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Blood carries nutrients, oxygen, water, and other substances, but not carbon dioxide.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The circulatory system consists of the heart, blood vessels, and skin.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
